<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ASISTEM</string>
    <string name="app_version">ALPHA 0.0.3</string>

    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="courses">Curses</string>
    <string name="saved">Saved</string>

    <!-- About -->
    <string name="image_logo_description">App logo image</string>
    <string name="image_contributor_description">Contributor avatar image</string>
    <string name="development">Development</string>
    <string name="development_name">Kyb3r Cipher</string>
    <string name="development_contact"><a href="https://kyb3rcipher.com">Contact</a></string>
    <string name="teacher">Teacher</string>
    <string name="teacher_name">Veronica Martinez Anaya</string>
    <string name="design">Design</string>
    <string name="designer_name">Benito</string>
    <string name="designer_contact"><a href="https://github.com/bengiv">@bengiv</a></string>

    <!-- Tap Pair -->
    <string name="button_check_name">Check</string>
    <string name="button_check_description">Check button</string>
    <string name="button_close_description">Close button</string>
    <string name="tapPair_title">Tap the pairs</string>

    <!-- Courses -->
    <!-- 1 -->
    <string name="courseImageDescription">Course Image</string>
    <string name="courseButtonDescription">Course button</string>
    <string name="course1Title">Fractures</string>
    <string name="course1Description">Assess, treat, and prevent complications in fracture injuries.</string>
    <string name="course2Title">Burns</string>
    <string name="course2Description">Assess, treat, and prevent complications in burn injuries..</string>
    <!-- exercise -->
    <string name="courseFracturesRead">
        Fractures are breaks in the bones and can range in severity from small cracks to completely broken bones. Common signs of a fracture include swelling, severe pain, deformity, inability to move the affected limb, and sometimes a popping or cracking sound at the time of the injury.
         If you suspect someone has a fracture, it is crucial to act quickly and take first aid measures:

         \n\n1. Evaluate the situation:
         \nKeep calm and secure the area to prevent further injury.
         Notify emergency services if the fracture is serious or if the injured person cannot move.

         \n\n2. Immobilize the affected area:
         \nAsk the injured person not to move the injured part to avoid further damage.
         If the person needs to be moved, try to immobilize the broken bone with splints, a makeshift splint, or simply hold the limb in the position you found it.

         \n\n3. Control swelling and pain:
         \nApply cold compresses or ice packs wrapped in a cloth to the affected area to reduce swelling and relieve pain.
         Do not apply ice directly to the skin, as it can cause frostbite damage.

         \n\n4. Seek medical attention:
         \nThe injured person should be taken to a medical facility or, in an emergency, call emergency services to evaluate them and provide appropriate treatment.
         It is essential to remember that moving a person with a serious fracture can aggravate the injury. It is always best to wait for healthcare professionals to move the person, unless there is imminent danger in the environment.

         \n\n
         Providing basic first aid for a fracture can help minimize pain and prevent further complications until appropriate medical care can be obtained.
    </string>


    <!-- Exercise -->
    <!-- options -->
    <string name="exerciseOptions_title">Select the answer</string>
    <!-- read -->
    <string name="exerciseRead_title">Read the text</string>
    <!-- select -->
    <string name="exerciseSelect_title">Select the correct option</string>
    <!-- write -->
    <string name="exerciseWrite_title">Write the answer</string>
    <!-- tap pairs -->
    <string name="exerciseTap_pairs">Tap the pairs</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>